

Portfolio: mrdoker1.github.io/portfolio

Email: <a href="mailto:fixrapdok@gmail.com">fixrapdok@gmail.com</a>

**Phone:** +375(29)216-91-79

### **SUMMARY**

I am a (UX/UI) User Experience & Interface Designer and Developer with a technical background and user-centred design thinking, working with E-commerce and SaaS-oriented projects.

My responsibility is to make products clear and helpful to people and make the team's development process smooth and transparent. I enjoy teamwork and am always happy to share knowledge.

#### **SKILLS**

Responsive Web Design, UX, UI Design;

Mobile Design (IOS,Android);

Motion Design;

Vector Illustration, Icons;

CJM, Sketching, Wireframing, UML Diagrams;

UX Audit, Competitor Analysis, Usability, AB Testing;

User-Centered Design, Jobs-To-Be-Done methodology;

Agile, Scrum/Kanban.

## TOOLS

Adobe Creative Suite (AI, PS, AE);

Figma, Sketch, XD;

Protopie, After Effects, Principle;

Miro,Figjam;

Axure RP, Invision, Marvel;

JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, Git;

Tilda, Readymag, other page builders;

YouTrack, Jira, Trello.

### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

User Experience: Principles and Processes

Agile with Atlassian Jira

JavaScript: Basics and Functions

HTML and CSS Fundamentals

Mad Rabbit Illustration Course

### **PUBLICATIONS**

How to Create Landing Pages in Magento?

What are the Latest Web Design Trends 2020?

Other Articles

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Andersen Lab / UI/UX designer

APR 2021 - PRESENT

Creating Web/Mobile Applications, CRM systems

Creating UX artifacts such as CJM, User Flows, User Stories, etc.

Creating sitemap and information architecture

Producing qualitative and quantitative research and usability testing

Designed social media graphics and digital marketing campaigns

Cross-platform design experience

Work in collaboration with key project team members, including tech leads,

Strategy, PMs, and creative leads

Experience working in an Agile development process

## **BeIVG** / UI/UX designer (E-commerce based)

JAN 2019 – APR 2021

Design stores based on Magento/Presta/WooCommerce/Shopify/osCommerce;

UX Audit, Research;

Wireframing, interaction prototypes design;

Building complex interfaces, UI design;

BeIVG Design System, UI Library, Custom Blocks Library;

Internal projects, website, style guides, marketing materials.

## Manao / Web Designer

MAR 2017 – JAN 2019

Designing information architecture and creating interactive prototypes;

Website design, applications design, landing pages;

Graphic design;

Illustration/icons and matte painting.

# Freelance Local, Upwork

MAY 2016 - MAR 2017

Upwork freelancer - UI Design, Web Design, Marketing, local Smile Coffee - Print, Web Dev, Brand Identity.

### **EDUCATION**

# **PSU**

Faculty of information technologies

SEP 2013 – AUG 2017

A bachelor's degree, Information Technology Software.